bomis.com 2005-12-10

# Bomis.Com Privacy Policy

  * Bomis doesn't personally care who you are. That's your business. 
  * Bomis does not collect personal information about visitors to this site, or about regular Bomis members. 
  * Bomis will never give away your email address. We will not sell it either. We will only email members specifically about their membership (e.g. the monthly newsletter). 
  * Security - we do not collect personal information so we cannot do anything nasty with it, since we don't have it. Bomis may place deliver cookie files to your browser, especially if you log in to the member area of our site. These cookie files may be used to track surfing patterns on our site. However, you remain anonymous, as we have no idea who belongs to which cookie. Information gleaned from this tracking of surfing patterns is not made available to any third party. 
  * If you want to make your email address available on a ring you make, you can do that. We personally don't care. That's your business. 
  * Contact -- You can contact Bomis by email at bomis@bomis.com. 
  * If you fill out a form or survey on Bomis with personal information then we will simply add up all the results to get some overall feel for who our visitors are. We use this information to squeeze money out of advertisers. But we would never reveal specific information about you to advertisers or anyone else. 

Now, go surf [Bomis](http://www.bomis.com/) in peace. 

|  Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick's Sonar Network, our Web advertising partner. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. Information about your visit to this site (but not your name, address, or other personal information) is used to serve ads to you on this site. This information is not collected by Sonar and DoubleClick for profiling. For more information about Sonar, cookies, and your right to "opt-out", please [click here](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm).
